[VARIANT]	[DESCRIPTION]	I_AUARV	I_LFARN	I_PSTYV	I_AUBED	I_AUZUS	I_ETBED	I_GRUAK	I_GRUAK_AIP	I_GRUAP	I_GRUAP_AIP	I_GRUET	I_GRUKD	I_GRUVS	I_PLMIN	I_POSVO	I_UPFLU
*		Copying control: Reference document type	Copying control: Target delivery type	Reference item category	Requirements for the order to be delivered	Requirement for combining orders in one delivery	Requirement relating to a schedule line to be delivered	Copying requirements for data transfer VBAK	Data trans. of header data from ext. system	Copying requirements for data transfer VBAP	Data transfer of item data from external system	Group requirement for schedule line data transfer	Copying requirements for transferring business data	Copying Requirements for Data Transfer VEKP	Quantity is calculated positively, negatively or not at all	Copy item number from reference	Update indicator for flow table
*REFERENCING																	
Var001	Variant 001	YQOR	LF	YBAB	#101	#000	#151	#000	#000	#101	#000	#151	#002	#000	#+		X
Var002	Variant 002	YQOR	LF	YSWP	#101	#000	#151	#000	#000	#101	#000	#151	#002	#000	#+		X
