[VARIANT]	[DESCRIPTION]	I_AUARV	I_AUBED	I_AUZUS	I_ETBED	I_GRUAK	I_GRUAK_AIP	I_GRUAP	I_GRUAP_AIP	I_GRUET	I_GRUKD	I_GRUPA	I_GRUVS	I_LFARN	I_PLMIN	I_POSVO	I_PSTYV	I_UPFLU
*		Copying control: Reference document type	Requirements for the order to be deliver	Requirement for combining orders in one	Requirement relating to a schedule line	Copying requirements for data transfer V	Data trans. of header data from ext. sys	Copying requirements for data transfer V	Data transfer of item data from external	Group requirement for schedule line data	Copying requirements for transferring bu	Copying requirements for partner data VB	Copying Requirements for Data Transfer V	Copying control: Target delivery type	Quantity is calculated positively, negat	Copy item number from reference	Reference item category	Update indicator for flow table
*REFERENCING		D52;I_AUART															D38;I_PSTYV	
Var001	Variant 001	DL	#000	#000	#000	#301	#000	#000	#000	#000	#000	#000	#000	LLR				
Var002	Variant 002	DLRE	#000	#000	#000	#301	#000	#000	#000	#000	#000	#000	#000	LLR				